Hello.
こんにちは
I know it's rude, but please take the time to interrupt me for about a minute at the beginning.
あつかましいですが、冒頭の1分ほど私に出しゃばる時間をいただ
I think it's okay.
けれ ばなぁと思っています
Dear viewers, while there are many works,
視聴者の皆さん、たくさん作品がある中、
Thank you very much for looking at this work and Manpiece's work.
こちらの作品だったり、マンピースの作品を見ていただき本当に
I'm grateful.
感謝 しています
I also read reviews,
レビューだったりも拝見させてもらってますけど、
Whether it's heartwarming words or harsh opinions,
心温かい言葉だったり、厳しい意見だったり、
While there are many comments and comments,
ご指摘など、たくさん声がある中、
I hope that you will take it seriously and let me learn from it.
真摯に受け止めさせてもらい、学ばせていただければなぁと思って
I'm here.
います
The content of the project, what they wanted me to do, etc.
企 画内容だったり、あれやってくれだったり、
I want to see this, I think it's better like this,
これ見たい、こうしたほうがいいよだったり、
I'm sure there are many, but my name is Yamanishi, so...
いっぱいあると思いますけど、私山西と申しますので、
If you could describe this Yamanishi,
この山西、なんなりと言っていただければ、
I will do what I can, so
できる範囲のことはさせていただきますので、
I think there are many areas for improvement,
改善点だったりもたくさんあると思いますけど、
I hope you can look at it with warm eyes,
温かい目で見ていただければなぁと思ってますので、
Thank you for your continued support.
今後ともどうぞよろしくお願いします
So, thank you for taking the time to talk.
で、喋る時間ありがとうございました
There were so many voices from everyone today.
今日の子はね、皆様の声がすごく多かった、
I called Yuki-chan, so please enjoy.
ゆきちゃんを呼び出したので、どうぞお楽しみください
Now, excuse me.
では、失礼します